Hey, Lorenzo. How's it feel, man? It's
been a family affair for the NFL draft
for you.
>> It's been great. It's been great. Felt
like the longest day ever. Um, but I'm
I'm super happy to go uh play with the
Saints.
>> When um how much kind of pre-draft uh
contact did you have with the team?
>> Um they came up um to Ohio State for
proday, day before proday. Uh so I got
to interact with them, go to dinner. All
the coaches there, the whole staff was
there. So I got to meet meet the whole
staff and um yeah, that's kind of the
relationship. And then also at the at
the comm line, I got to meet with them
as well.
>> How did you feel like all that went and
and what was sort of your impression of
the Saints staff?
>> They were all welcoming. Um
I I'm just I can't I couldn't be more
excited, man. Uh great staff. It was I'm
excited to go work with a lot of the
guys in that room. Know some of the guys
all a lot of the players, Tyler, uh
Audrey, some of the guys I play with the
for text me. So it seems like a lot of
love. I'm excited. Lorenzo, you ran the
the 42 when it was reported that you
weren't fully healthy when you did that.
What do you what do you actually run?
>> I probably could have ran a little bit
faster, but that's what that's what I
have for that day. So, I don't know.
Maybe a little bit faster.
>> Do humans run faster than 42 or like
>> what?
>> Can people actually run faster than 42?
What? Like what are we talking about
here? Like what's
>> not I probably could have ran low 42.
The thing that got me was the jump just
because I had to jump with my left arm
instead of my right style a little bit
different. So, I feel like I could have
jumped a higher there for sure, but I
don't know, man.
>> How is your shoulder now? And what's
kind of the rehab process like for you?
>> Yeah, I have a great team at Ohio State
that's been taking care of me this whole
draft process. Uh, shout out Adam
Stewart. Um, and then, uh, Ryan Rock was
my surgeon. So, on track. I'm excited to
be I'm going to be ready to go.
>> There's a lot of different timelines
that are kind of flipping around. What's
the timeline that you're expecting right
now that you're working with?
>> Uh, I'm going to go in uh, still be
working with the team. It's going to be
really really up to them. I'm going to
be ready for when it's time for camp,
when it's time to compete. Uh when jobs
and stuff are on the line and I got to
show it's time to really play, uh that's
when I'm going to be ready to go.
>> So, how did your expectation is to be
ready for training camp? Is that
>> Yes, sir.
>> How did you accept the news that you
were going from wide receiver to safety?
I mean, was that something good? And how
did that help you as a safety?
>> Yes, sir. I feel like being able to
understand route con. I used to run
those route concepts, how I wanted to
attack a defense, how I wanted to attack
uh DBs. So I feel like my overall my my
football acumen has just increased
especially working here with being on
the default ball with Matt Patricia Tim
Wall and Matt Guerrer and this Ohio
State staff feel like it's prepared me
well for the NFL and really the position
switch as well just all those tools
about to come together here at the
safety position position really whatever
whatever the team needs me to do special
teams even as well.
>> Are you aware of the Ohio State to New
Orleans pipeline that has existed for
some time and what you're carrying on
here? I'm really not too familiar with
Aldo House. I know my boy Chris Ave is
there. Uh great player, but overall I'm
excited to keep that pipeline going
though for sure.
>> And how much time have you spent in New
Orleans, if at all.
>> I haven't been I haven't been. So I'm
excited to get down there, go down to
the South. Uh really only been in the
Midwest my whole life. So excited for
the change scenery, new people, new
environment.
>> Was there a player you wanted to style
after as a kid?
>> Uh I wouldn't say so. I'm definitely
just trying to play like me. I feel like
I'm in a unique situation just my skill
set and different things like that. Uh
there's a lot of players in the NFL. I
like some like ball hawking guys like
Xavier McKenna, guys who can move around
like McDuffy, uh Shamari Connor,
different guys like that. But I'm really
for my own play style, being able to
have range, be able to go down and cover
three, uh special teams, be able to get
the ball in my hands and be effective in
that way. So feel like my play style
it's it's me, Lorenzo Styles.
Did uh how come you didn't return more
kicks and is that something teams have
talked to you about doing?
>> Yeah. So, how State they had this thing
where they like putting receivers back
there, offensive guys. So, I was coach,
let me get a chance, especially coach,
let me get a chance. So, the first time
I got back there, I was like probably
five like way too deep. Wasn't supposed
to take it out and uh I knew if I
touched the ball, I was taken to the end
zone. So, I'm exc I'm really excited for
the NFL and how uh how important that is
in field position, especially in the NFL
game.
That was like the first Ohio State kick
return touchdown in like 15 years or
something like that. Is that right?
>> Yeah, that's correct.
>> Well, how did it feel to be a part of
that history?
>> It felt great. Um, our special teams, we
were really trying to work on that part
of our game and keep continue to improve
just being able to impact the game and
then the my teammates did a great job.
Uh, and the the coach Nate Edner who
played in the NFL special player for a
long long time. It was great to um be
able to have that success alongside him.
Lawrence, what was it like, you know,
growing up in your house with your
brother? How much uh influence your dad
have on you?
>> He started that football that football
fire that's still within us, with my
brother and within me. Uh we were
competitive. It wasn't necessarily about
um like he didn't really talk about his
his career necessarily, but he instilled
all the things of what it's like to be a
pro that we now recognize as we're
older.
>> Were you hoping to be drafted with your
brother or are you glad you get to go
elsewhere? How are you kind of feeling
about going into this? Yeah. Uh, I'm
ready to start my my own legacy. We all
both, we have the Styles family. He has
his, he has I have mine. So, I'm excited
to be in a situation where as a player,
it's him to compete against each other.
I'll be on the opposite side, then
hopefully down the line. Uh, maybe he
can come to the Saints and we'll be able
to to ball together down the line.
>> Lorenzo, how familiar are you with the
way that Brandon Staley utilizes sort of
the star slot role and and and is that a
position you feel that you could see
yourself in?
>> Yes, sir. me and coach Patricia. So, we
were doing some uh just watching
different games. So, uh I watch coach a
lot and um yeah, I feel like I'm going
to be like being able to be versatile in
the defense, being able to run different
two high structures, uh play the deep
path, play the post when we get when we
uh rotate to three. Um I'm I'm excited.
I got a lot to learn. Um but I'm I'm
excited.
>> How do you feel about potentially
rushing the passer?
>> I mean, you're going to see the 4-2 show
up there. Uh have a good disguise. They
won't be able to see me coming. I feel
like it's going to be another element to
help the defense out.
>> Lorenzo, you graduated with your father.
It says here, "What was that day like
for you?"
>> No, that meant a lot. So, my dad went
back. He's actually So, to coach in
college football, you have to have your
degree and that's something he wanted to
do for a long time. So, being able to
see him and it it was fun. He took
school so serious. He was a dude high
GPA, all A's type of guy. But, uh, being
able to graduate with him, being able to
see him coaching, he's coaching at
Bowling Green now along his former
teammate Eddie George. Um it's uh how
far the whole family's came and
everyone's chasing their dreams. So it's
uh it's great for all of everything
we've been praying and manifesting come
to fruition.
>> Coming from a football family the way
that you do, how would you describe your
work ethic away from the football field?
>> I love football. Um it's really it's my
life being professional. I feel like I'm
I'm excited to spend 13 14 hours in the
facility today. I'm excited to keep
getting better every single year. Um I
love attacking the game. Uh yeah, I I
love it. There's nothing else uh nothing
else I want to be